officegreeting.com 2014-07-02

# Office Greeting - Privacy

#### OfficeGreeting.com Privacy Policy

* * *

_Last Updated December 2012_

OVERVIEW

At OfficeGreeting.com, protecting our users' privacy and security is a top priority. For this reason, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of your choices regarding the use of your personal information online. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, under what circumstances we disclose it to third-parties, and your rights to update or correct it.

INFORMATION ABOUT YOU 

Information Gathered From All Visitors

Aggregate Data

We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. These statistics are very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use this type of data in aggregate-that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical "ratings" about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business ("Business Partners"). We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.

3rd-Party Login Systems

We use 3rd-Party Login & Authentication systems to validate user accounts on site. These include the Linkedin API, the Facebook API and others. In each case, we abide by the terms of service of each 3rd-Party API. We do not collect usernames and passwords for these services, or any information that is not allowed under the API terms of service. By using our site and authenticating via any such 3rd-Party Login API, you are granting us access to your profile information contained within that 3rd-Party site. You are also agreeing to abide by the privacy policy and terms of service of that 3rd-Party site. For more information, please consult the policies of the 3rd-Party API service that you used to login to our site. 

Cookies

We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. For example, cookies allow us to recognize you when you re-enter our web site so that you will not have to sign-in each time you visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on our web site if you choose not to accept cookies.

Activity on the Site 

We are using Google Analytics service to gain insight into our customers' use of the site. Google Analytics may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, and scrolling activity on this website. Google Analytics does not collect personally identifiable information from this website. 

IP Addresses

We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message. We may be required to do this if compelled by law or to investigate abuse of our service. 

When You Send A Greeting

If you use our web site to send an online greeting or any other content, we collect your e-mail address, your name, your 3rd-Party profile information and your list of contacts. Your greeting or content will typically be delivered via the messaging functionality available to us by the 3rd-Party Login service that you have used (such as Facebook, Linkedin, Google etc). This information is necessary to send the content and provide confirmation that it has been received. We may also use your e-mail address to contact you if you have chosen to receive communications from OfficeGreeting.com or its Partners. Information on your recipient list is not stored on our servers, and will be fetched again each time you send a greeting or content to your list. 

Communications from OfficeGreeting.com

We send to all of our users our exclusive OfficeGreeting.com Newsletter, which alerts you to new features, content, and services, premiums available on our site. From time to time, we will also send you invitations to enhance your OfficeGreeting.com membership, offers for new products and services from OfficeGreeting.com, special "Members Only" premiums, or special offers from our affiliates and sponsors. These communications are sent to you directly by OfficeGreeting.com. We do not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties in connection with the Newsletter. You can always decline the Newsletter by configuring your account settings on the site. 

Mandatory Communications

OfficeGreeting.com reserves the right to communicate with you from time to time about important administrative, policy, legal, credit card, and billing matters, which will affect your use of our web sites, including without limitation any alleged violations of our Terms of Service. These communications are mandatory.

Information Gathered From Members

If you elect to upgrade your account and purchase a Premium Membership or redeem a promotional membership on OfficeGreeting.com, you may be required to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number, expiration date, and billing address (this required information is subject to change from time to time). Additional data may be collected from Members based upon certain services they elect to utilize on our web site. 

OfficeGreeting.com'S USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have provided us your consent, we will use the information we have collected about you in five ways:

To send personalized, targeted information that we think our users will find relevant from OfficeGreeting.com;

  * To include targeted advertising within such messages;
  * To send promotions and coupons based on the user's interests;
  * To contact the user for feedback and surveys; and
  * To send the user other information about OfficeGreeting.com.

Privacy of Greeting Card Information

We treat all of our greetings products as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and will not disclose the contents of any greeting other than to the intended recipient, except under the specific situations outlined in Disclosure Exceptions, below. Please keep in mind that when you send a greeting card to 1 recipient (such as on their birthday), the greeting message will only be visible to the 1 recipient. When you send a greeting card to multiple recipients (such as on a holiday), the greeting message will be visible to all intended recipients. The identity of the recipient is verified by requiring authentication through one of the 3rd-Party Login options provided. This provides further security and privacy to your eCard and ensures that only intended recipient(s) view your message. 

Disclosure Exceptions

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third-parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary:

  * To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order;
  * To protect the company's rights and property;
  * To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages;
  * To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or the OfficeGreeting.com service; or
  * During emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.
  * Under certain circumstances, recipients, their legal representatives, and/or law enforcement authorities may be able to combine this with information disclosed by ISPs to determine the source of a particular communication. By using this service, you knowingly and voluntarily assume any risks associated with such disclosure.

YOUR CONTROL OVER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Opt-Out/Changing Your Status At any time, you can change choices you have previously made as to the use of your personal information. Every communication OfficeGreeting.com sends you will contain a clearly worded "Opt-Out" or "Unsubscribe" link allowing you to withdraw your permission for future mailings. Please allow five to seven days for processing. 

Editing Your Profile

If you are a registered member, you have the ability to review and correct your personally identifiable information at any time. Simply sign into the site and click on account settings. 

OTHER MATTERS

Protection For Children - COPPA Compliance We are committed to protecting the privacy and rights of children online. We believe that children should be able to use the Internet in a safe, productive, and efficient manner and should be afforded the highest protection available with respect to their personal information. To that end, we have made it our policy to not collect any individually identifiable information from users whom we know are under the age of 13. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") imposes certain requirements upon web sites and online services that are directed toward children. To learn more about COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission COPPA Web Site.

Sale of Assets

In the event that OfficeGreeting.com and/or its units or subsidiaries are ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized, or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third-party acquiring OfficeGreeting.com's assets. In the event we do so, we will place a prominent notice of the sale on the homepage of our site, with links to information as to how you can change your privacy preferences.

Data Security

When you place orders for purchased products or access your payment information, we use an advanced encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, a lock or key icon appears on the bottom of your web browser. In addition to our online security efforts, we take steps to protect your personal data offline, as well. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Employees are granted access on a need-to-know basis (for example, our billing clerk or a customer support representative). Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment using industry-standard protections. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy

OfficeGreeting.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. When OfficeGreeting.com posts changes to this Policy, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of OfficeGreeting.com Sites. 

As always, if you have any questions, please feel free to contact us using the form on the site.
